[
	{
		"id": "1",
		"question": "Who was the first President of the United States?",
		"answer": "George Washington"
	},
		{
		"id": "2",
		"question": "When did Columbus set sail?",
		"answer": "1492"
	},
		{
		"id": "3",
		"question": "What is the nearest star to Earth besides the sun?",
		"answer": "Alpha Centauri"
	},
		{
		"id": "4",
		"question": "What celestial body did Bahaumut emerge from?",
		"answer": "The Moon"
	},
		{
		"id": "5",
		"question": "Who originally summoned Bahamut?",
		"answer": "The Meracydia"
	},
		{
		"id": "6",
		"question": "What mortal did the Goddess Morgan inhabit before returning to the mortal plane?",
		"answer": "Tieve"
	},
		{
		"id": "7",
		"question": "Who removed the hand of Luke Skywalker?",
		"answer": "Darth Vader"
	},
		{
		"id": "8",
		"question": "What is the oath of the Dragoon?",
		"answer": "Res please!"
	},
		{
		"id": "9",
		"question": "What is the oath of the Black Mage?",
		"answer": "Healers Adjust!"
	},
		{
		"id": "10",
		"question": "What is the oath of the Healers?",
		"answer": "DON'T STAND IN THE FIRE!"
	},
		{
		"id": "11",
		"question": "Where was the Soul stone located before Thanos acquired it?",
		"answer": "Vormir"
	},
		{
		"id": "12",
		"question": "Xbox or Playstation?",
		"answer": "PC"
	},
		{
		"id": "13",
		"question": "Who is Jinx's sibling?",
		"answer": "Vi"
	},
		{
		"id": "14",
		"question": "Who is responsible for Sylas breaking free?",
		"answer": "Lux"
	},
		{
		"id": "15",
		"question": "Who can beat Superman?",
		"answer": "Doomsday"
	},
		{
		"id": "16",
		"question": "Who has partted the clouds with a single punch?",
		"answer": "Saitama"
	},
		{
		"id": "17",
		"question": "What is the end of the world?",
		"answer": "Apocalypse"
	},
		{
		"id": "18",
		"question": "How do true men solve problems?",
		"answer": "1v1 Final Destination, No items, Fox only"
	},
		{
		"id": "19",
		"question": "Who is responsible for Zenos nearly destroying all of reality?",
		"answer": "Goku"
	},
		{
		"id": "20",
		"question": "What does a Psychiatrist say?",
		"answer": "How do you feel about that?"
	},
		{
		"id": "21",
		"question": "Who was the first man on the moon?",
		"answer": "Neil Armstrong"
	},
		{
		"id": "22",
		"question": "Who blinded Glas Ghaibhleann?",
		"answer": "Kai"
	},
		{
		"id": "23",
		"question": "What did Kheaghan become to defeat the Dragon of Time?",
		"answer": "Cichol"
	},
		{
		"id": "24",
		"question": "What did Thanos throw at Tony Stark?",
		"answer": "A moon"
	},
		{
		"id": "25",
		"question": "What is the most powerful servant class?",
		"answer": "Saber"
	}
]